const DATA = [
    {

        story: ` `,
        qha: [
            {
                question: 'Something that anyone can see but cant stole?',
                dataString: ' It increases by sharing.',
                correctAnswer: `knowledge`
            },
            {
                question: 'Who i am ,i have eyes but cant see ,i have a mouth but cant talk,have legs but cant walk,who am i?',
                dataString: 'I\'m a Barbie girl, in the Barbie world.',
                correctAnswer: `doll`
            },
            {
                question: 'I can write but i am not pen,I can walk but i am not any vehicle,I can tik-tok but i am not clock, who am i?',
                dataString: 'Christopher Latham Sholes',
                correctAnswer: `typewriter`
            },
            {
                question: 'Titar ke do aage teetar ,Titar ke do piche teetar, age teetar ,piche teetar ,bolo kitne teetar?',
                dataString: 'Find the answer for every phrase.',
                correctAnswer: `2213`
            },
            {
                question: 'rhenium ,Nitrogen, calcium  , thoriumm , beryllium ?',
                dataString: 'Rearrange me if you can.',
                correctAnswer: `caren beth`
            },
        ]
    },
    {

        story: ` `,
        qha: [
            {
                question: 'Gussa mat kar nao-jawan ,Andhi ho ya tufan,garmi sardi ka nhi bhan ,Bol me',
                dataString: 'Kiske hai ye bol?',
                correctAnswer: `lal bahadur sastri chowk`
            },
            {
                question: 'Sagar kinare Dil ke pukare vahi hote hai lohe ke machhware..',
                dataString: 'Jahaz kaha banaye jate hai',
                correctAnswer: `dockyard`,
                optionalAnswer: `shipyard`
            },
            {
                question: 'Pahad ko Jaye Ram Jab ,Banvas se aaye ram tabhi to rawan sharan me aaye',
                dataString: 'Batao Batao konsi jagah thi vo..',
                correctAnswer: `lanka niwas`
            },
            {
                question: ``,
                dataString: 'Carefully see the hints',
                correctAnswer: `284`
            },
        ]
    },
    {

        story: ` `,
        qha: [
            {
                question: 'Guess the PassCode to deactivate the bomb',
                dataString: '7 letter word.',
                correctAnswer: `rajveer`
            },
            {
                question: 'Who had informed Byomkesh about Natasha?',
                dataString: 'Who called Byomkesh ?',
                correctAnswer: `rashmika`,
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        story: ` ` ,
        question:`Give conclusion of story ,in your word?`
    }
]

export default DATA;
